Francis A.Gregory
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Francis A.Gregory Genealogical Collection
1902-1975
DC Public Library, Special Collections
2.5 linear feet; 6 boxes
005
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Shaed Family, 1902-1975
  - Shaed Family fact sheet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cenos Detwyler Shaed - biographical sketch, 1880-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gregory W. Shaed photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alice Evelyn Shaed biographical sketch/photos/memorabilia, 1902-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ernestine Pamela Shaed photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Helen Virginia Shaed (Waters) photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gregory W. Shaed, Jr. photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Lee L. Shaed (Proctor) photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Eunice J. Shaed (Newton) photos and memorabilia, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dunbar High School, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alice and Ernestine Shaed Elementary School, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Isham G. Newton, Sr. and Amanda E. Stockton (parents of Eunice Shaed’s husband), Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Raymond E. Waters, Sr. and family (husband of Helen Shaed), Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - “The five Shaed sisters of Washington, D.C.: Elementary school educators”, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Series 2: Baltimore Family, 1902-1987
  - The Cadet, 24th Regiment, High School Cadets, Washington, D.C., Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Washington Chapter of Girl Friends, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong Training School Yearbook, 1902-1903 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Charles H. Baltimore, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photo of Bishop Albert Johnson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan AME Church, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Thelma Baltimore, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Deanwood Schools, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Minnie Shumate Woodson, The Sable Curtain, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Joe Louis scrapbook, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Encyclopaedia of African Methodism, Volume 1 by R.R. Wright, Jr., Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Clarence S. Greene and Evelyn Gardiner Greene, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dunbar High School Yearbooks (property of Belle Manonicee Sadgwar), Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dunbar Class of 1927 50th Anniversary commemorative book, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series 3: Elzie Schubert Hoffman, 1898-1976
  - “A Collection of.. Materials.. Setting Forth the Life and Times of Washington, D.C. Musician, Elzie Schubert Hoffman”, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)